http://www.waterpeople.com.au/terms-conditions

Our response to the COVID-19 pandemic.Learn moreAbout UsBuy FiltersRentalsProduct ReviewsResource CentreCall the experts(03) 9885 02220Your Cart$0.00: RemoveSubtotalPay with browser.Continue to CheckoutNo items found.Product is not available in this quantity.MenuProduct TypesWater TypesIndustriesProduct FinderServicingBrandsContactAbout UsBuy FiltersRentalsProduct ReviewsResource Centre(03) 9885 0222View Cart0Your Cart$0.00: RemoveSubtotalPay with browser.Continue to CheckoutNo items found.Product is not available in this quantity.Product TypesProduct TypesWash StationsFiltered Water TapsWater CoolersDrinking FountainsWall MountedReverse OsmosisCountertopUndersink FiltersCrocksAlkalisersFaucets & TapwareBath & ShowerWhole HouseWater TypesWater TypesChilledBoilingAmbientChilled & BoilingChilled & AmbientBoiling & AmbientSparklingAll-in-OneBoiled, Chilled & SparklingIndustriesIndustriesEducationCafés and RestaurantsAged CareGym and Sports ClubsOfficeHealthcareProduct FinderServicingBrandsContactTerms & ConditionsHome|Terms & ConditionsDelivery and Refund PolicyOnce payment has been received, we will ship your order within 2 business days if your ordered product is in stock. If it is not in stock, we will immediately advise your estimated shipping date.For online purchases, we will also provide you with a 30 day guarantee that should you change your mind for any reason whatsoever, we will refund your full purchase price.To qualify for the refund you must return the product to us in an unused and undamaged condition, with original packaging.Currency PolicyAll prices on The Water People site are in Australian Dollars.Privacy and SecurityThe Water People understands that people may be concerned about how their personal information that companies collect is used and accordingly The Water People is committed to ensuring the privacy and security of any information that the company holds about its customers.The Water People respects your privacy. We do not sell, rent or loan any identifiable information regarding our customers to any third party. We may use and share aggregated information when it enables us to improve our product and service offering. Any information you give us is held with the utmost care and security.The Water People asks you for specific pieces of personal information when you register as a customer. The Water People will not collect any personal information about such individuals except when provided by such individuals.Website SecurityAll payments on The Water People website are processed using eWay or Paypal. Eway is a secure payment gateway and uses 128 bits SSL to encrypt your confidential information for transit from your computer over internet. We also use Paypal which allows you to shop with peace of mind using your secure Paypal account.The Water People do not collect and / or store your credit card details.Personal Account InformationYour name, delivery detail, telephone number, email address help The Water People to deliver your order on time to the correct location. We confirm by email the items in your order, the scheduled delivery window you've selected and the delivery address. A Customer Service Representative may contact you by telephone to resolve any questions we might have about your order.The Water People will not reveal your personal information to any third party unless required to do so by law.CookiesA cookie is a small file created by your web browser (eg. Internet Explorer v.5) to assign a unique identification to your computer. The Water People’s financial transaction pages use the cookie to keep track of items in your shopping trolley, we do not use cookies to retrieve personal information about you from your computer. To shop, you need to have the cookies option of your browser turned on. However, once you've finished shopping, you can delete cookies from your hard drive if you like.IP AddressThe Water People logs IP addresses for systems administration purposes. IP addresses are logged to track a user's session and help us determine how often the areas of our site are visited. In many cases, we view and discard the information immediately. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable so we could never link an IP address to a specific customer.Online Surveys and ContestsFrom time to time, The Water People may conduct online surveys that ask you for demographic data, like household information, ages, and so on. Participation in these surveys is always voluntary. The Water People aggregates the responses we receive before using the information to improve the product offering and services we offer The Water People may also offer contests that ask for some personal information, such as name and email address, so that we can contact winners. All of these contests follow applicable gaming regulations. We will clearly post the rules and terms of each contest on the site.Changing and Editing Your InformationYou can make changes to your personal information or to your customer status by emailing us at admin@thewaterpeople.com.au, noting the changes required. Finally, you could contact us by phone. Currently, we do not send out any regularly scheduled email communications to customers. If we were to introduce such communications, we would provide customers with the option to not receive such emails.NoteThe Water People reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If it is changed, the changes will be posted on The Water People’s web site so that you are always aware of the sort of information collected, how the information may be used, and under what circumstances it may be disclosed by The Water People. Please note that if at any time The Water People is required by law to release information about you or your organisation, The Water People must cooperate fully. This Privacy Policy does not apply to acts or practices of The Water People that are directly related to employee records of current or former employees.© Copyright 2020 The Water People. Site by Digital360ContactFAQsTerms & ConditionsWarrantyNew Touch Free Drinking Fountain ConverterView Product
